https://www.expressflags.com/privacy-policy

My Account
Register
Login
Wish List (0)
MILITARY
U.S. Military Flags - Outdoor Polyester (Good)
U.S. Military Flags - Outdoor Nylon (Better)
U.S. Military Flags - Outdoor Poly-Max
(Best)
U.S. Military Flag Indoor Display Sets
U.S. Military Stick Mounted Flags
Blue Star Service Banners
American Veterans Commemorative Flags, Retired Flags, Misc. Military Flags
U.N. Member Country Flags - 193 Flags Complete Sets
O.A.S.
Residential Flagpoles - Outdoor
Indoor Display Flagpoles, Parade Flagpoles, Parade Accessories
Flagpole Accessories, Flagpole Hardware
+-
MORE
MORE
INFORMATION LINKS:- Shipping Information- Track Order- Return Policy- Return Form- Special Promotions- Gift Certificates- Loyalty Rewards Program- Sitemap- FAQs
Indoor Flagpole Accessories
Flagpole Floor Stands - Indoor Displays
Outdoor Flagpole Accessories
Indoor and Parade Flagpole Ornaments
Brackets, Holders, Mounts, Pole Holders, Pole Hardware
Pennant Strings
Bicycle Safety Flags
Stick Mounted Flags
Gift Certificates
INFORMATION LINKS:- Shipping Information- Track Order- Return Policy- Return Form- Special Promotions- Gift Certificates- Loyalty Rewards Program- Sitemap- FAQs
Home
Privacy Policy
Information
About Us
Loyalty Rewards Program
Privacy Policy
Shipping Information
Return Policy
Site Map
FREE SHIPPING on orders of $70 or more - Low $8.95 flat rate for orders up to $69.99, some restrictions apply, click for details.       BBB Rating: A+
Privacy Policy
We created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website.
We Value Your Privacy - We do not sell or rent your information under any circumstances.
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to help identify you and your shopping cart and to gather broad demographic information. Our site uses cookies to keep track of your shopping cart.
This site may contain links to other sites. ExpressFlags.com / Advanced Advertising Graphics, Inc. is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.
Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect visitor's contact information (like their email address) and financial information (like their account or credit card numbers). Contact information from the order form is used to send orders and information about our company to our customers. The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services.
Security
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor.
This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service.
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact
ExpressFlags.com© 2020 Division of AAG, Inc.
